I want to show you how can you iterate
UI implementation in cursor very easily
and effective as we get new model like
cloud 4 models coding capability for UI
is become much better but once I really
miss implementing UI in cursor compared
with platform like v0ero is the
versioning it will lock all the
different versions as it goes so I can
jump in between different versions
compare the difference and forks from
the ones I prefer more and the nature of
design is that we often will iterate
multiple different versions of the same
screen until we find a version that we
really like. I just found this open
source plugin recently called Yoyo that
allow you to do this version control
directly in the AI ID like cursor wins
serve and cloud code and this speed ups
the UI iterations much faster and it's
also very good for code maintenance as
well because quite often when you prompt
cursor to do something it might just go
off rail and break a lot of stuff. So
you almost want some sort of quick
snappy save that you can easily go back
something more lightweight than git. And
here is my UI iteration workflow with
yoyo. So I can just click a button to
install extension. Normally I firstly go
to different platform to find design
inspirations. Their platform like
dribble where you can just go and find
some good UI reference as well as mobile
where they provide you real mockups of
applications or specific UI elements.
Let's say I found a UI that I quite
like. I can just take screenshot here
and paste into cursor give from UI
senior front end engineer designer we
want to build a digital web application
UI just like attached moch please first
break down and analyze design system
style font and components and let's
firstly build a UI mo with mock data on
the first page so it will try to analyze
the design style font and colors okay
now it has first version built in and we
can copy this URL and do command shift P
uh search for simple browser and paste
in the URL. This will allow you to just
preview the UI here directly in cursor
which is very helpful. So this is the
first version of the UI. As you can see
it's kind of 80% and got essence of UI
but it's not like 100%. And I also want
to like experiment with a few different
versions of styles. And this is where
this version control is really useful
for iterating UI. So I can create a new
version by clicking on this button. This
will create a snapshot of the codebase
at this specific point. Uh and I can
give it like initial UI. Then I can
start iterating the UI. Let's say I want
to iterate the component cards at top.
The cards at top should look like a moch
here. But currently it is not even
aligned and the color is wrong. For the
event card, I can copy paste and give a
prompt for task car. Please polish your
UI to look exactly same as the
screenshot. So we did some finetuning
and polish of the UI. I can click on
save new version here to save a newer
version of the UI and this how version
going to help on the UI iteration. I can
click on the V1 again and refresh the
simple browser. This allow me to see
what the original version was and I can
click back to the V2 and take a look at
the latest version. So you can like go
back and forth between those different
iterations very easily and see which one
is your favorite. And I can make a few
more changes now. Help me make a light
mode version, not dark mode version. So
I got the light version here. And I can
still again save the version. And I can
also add some custom nodes here. So this
will be the light version. Previously
will be polished dark version. I can
switch different type of UI quite easily
to see which one do I like. And I can
even make some more dramatic change. For
example, Apple introduced this kind of
liquid glass type of style recently. I
can just go find some liquid glass
implementation on GitHub and here we got
a one. So I can go to the CSS here and
just copy the whole style here and give
a prompt. Please help me update the
whole UI with Apple's new liquid glass
style. Below is some reference which is
CSS I just paste in. Now we get this
type of new liquid glass type of style
application. Obviously, you can keep
fine-tuning the UI to make it looks
better. And again, I can save the
version and you can see some description
be automatically added about liquid
glass. And what's really cool about this
new version control is that it manually
kept a lot of different versions. You
can actually chat to extension to
understand what does each version
contains and find a specific branch that
made certain change. Like here, I can
just give a prompt which version was
initial light mode. it will
automatically return me the right
version as well as some description
about what exactly we did in that
specific version. And this I think is
just touching what the new git or
versioning experience could be in the
era of AI coding. There's also a very
interesting interview between YC and the
founder of wingsf where they talk about
how git might be different. Have you
thought at all about whether doing git
commit all the time is the right move or
whether there needs to be like a deeper
infrastructure change? Yeah, I think we
have. So, you know, one of the things
that we always think of is in the future
you're going to have many many agents
running in parallel on your codebase.
That has some some trade-offs, right? If
you have two agents that kind of modify
the same piece of code at the same time,
it's hard to actually know what's going
That's another thing is that like it's
hard to have multiple branches checked
out at the same time with different
agents working on them independently.
All the merge conflicts. Oh god, there's
a lot of If you're interested in this
topic, I definitely recommend you go
check out and imagine what the future
might look like. Meanwhile, if you want
to learn about AI coding beyond basics,
I'm building this platform called AI
builder club where I will share the
latest workflow tips and learnings about
AI coding and building production ready
agents both myself and other industry
experts as well as tools that can help
you get start with your AI software much
faster like SAS launch kit and MCP boy
play. If you're interested, you can
click on the link in the description
below to join. I hope you enjoy this
video. Thank you and I see you next